Guide to the Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records, 1958-2000.
Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records
- Series IV Projects
  - Ground Screen Project
    - Goldsmith Files, 1991
      - Ground Screen Gap, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - Ground Screen - Spillover, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - Ground Screen Misc., 1991 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Heating Facility
    - HF Facility Proposal, Nov 1975 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence 1978-1983 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence 1984-1999 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - HF Facility Land Lease w/ the Puerto Rican Land Authority, 1978-99 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Cano Tiburones Wetlands, 1998-02 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Hurricane Georges, 9-21-98 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Various Projects
    - Planning & contracting for new optical/lidar lab, 1996-97 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - TAMI - Plan for Research of the Atmosphere & Ionosphere, 1/96 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Report on the Concept Development for an Upper Atmospheric Research Facility at the Arecibo Geomagnetic Conjugate Point in Argentina, 4/06 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - University of Puerto Rico - UPR Internet2 Project, Mar 1999 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Seismic Risk Survey, EQE International, 10/99 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Goldsmith files: AO Projects
      - Goldsmith Records: Weekly Info, Sept-Dec 2000 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Goldsmith Records: Weekly Info, Jan-Apr 2001 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Goldsmith Records: Weekly Info, May-Dec 2001 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Goldsmith Records: Weekly Info, Jan-June 2002 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Goldsmith Records: Weekly Info, July-Dec 2002 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Suspended Structure Weight Measurements, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - CNOC, Cornell-NAIC Oversight Committee, 2002-03 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - An Analysis of RF Field Levels at the Arecibo Observatory, 6-8-04 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - KTA-Tator, Inc., Coating Recommendations for the Suspended Structural Steel on the Radio Telescope at Arecibo Observatory, 8-26-05 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Kris Merschrod Review, Report of Activities, Accomplishments & Recommendations, Assignment to Review Organizational Development, 8-11-05 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - O'Brien & Gere - Tank Farm, Tank Farm Dry Well Closure Plan, July 2006, Dry Well Closure Report - Tank Farm Area, 1-29-07 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Lucius Pitkin, Inc., Ultrasonic inspection report, 3-13-06 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Spensieri Painting, Price & Technical Proposal, Telescopic Painting, 3-8-06 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Setup and Test Procedures for Mark IV Board, Ingrid Stairs, 6-9-96 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Arecibo / VLBI, 1977-2001
      - Correspondence, 1977-2001 (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Propagation Effects in Space VLBI, Leonid Gurvits, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - VLBI Recorder, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Other Equipment
    - 42-ft Collapsible/Portable Telescope, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Fine Guidance System, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Higuillales Antenna, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - RFI detection - IC8500-03 Receiver (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Distomat survey instruments, Mar 1991 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Atomic Hydrogen Maser, Sigma Tau Standards, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - JPL & SIgnma Tau Hydrogen Masers, 1996-2001 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Request for Duty-Free Entry of Scientific Instruments, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Air Inflated Structure, 1986, 1990
      - General Correspondence & Meeting minutes, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - Pre-Proposal documents, 1986, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - Cornell Facilities Management correspondence, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 33)
      - Budgets & Payments, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 34)
      - Invitation to Proposer's, Mar 1986 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - New Instrumentation, 1981-89
      - New Instrumentation, 1981-82 (Box 44, Folder 36)
      - New Instrumentation, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 37)
      - New Instrumentation, 1984-85 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Arecibo Instrumentation Plans Meeting, 6/8/89 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Los Canos Antenna, corres., 1985 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - A.O.'s South Site Farm, 1987-95 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Jeff Mock spectrometer prime agreement, 2-09-06 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Visiting Scientist Quarters
    - New VSQ - Corres. 1994, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Proposal for New VSQ Units, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Visitor Center
    - Request for Proposal, Visitor & Educational Facility, 2/6/95 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Cornell Facilities Job Orders, 2/92 & 2/97 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Visitor Center Report 2004-05 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Learning center
    - PAR for Expansion of the Educational Facilities at the Arecibo Observatory, 9/99 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Angel Ramos Foundation funding, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Learning Center - Accounts, 1999-2001 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Cornell's Role in Arecibo and NAIC, Hal Craft, (no date) (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Don Campbell viewgraphs Arecibo 2003-04 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Summer students' deaths at Arecibo, 6-21-03 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Interoffice correspondence, 1999-2004 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Feeds
    - 430 MHz Feed, 1969-1972 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Scale Model Tetst of 49.8 MHz Feed System, 6/75 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - 2380 MHz feed, 1975-76 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - 1420 MHz & 1670 MHz Parametric Amplifiers, 1973, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - 2270 MHz Receiver System for NASA, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - 1415 MHz Dual Polarizaed Feed, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - 1120 MHz Feed, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - 932 MHz Feed, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - 430 MHz Feed Insert, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1979-86 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Some Design Considerations for a 40.12 Mc/s Feed for the 1000-ft Diameter Reflector, D. Yabsley, 3/63 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Some Experiments with Models of a 40.12 Mc/s Feed for the 1000-ft Diameter Reflector, D. Cunnold, 1/64 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Calibration of the 1000-ft Arecibo Radio Reflector, R. Forrest, 9/65 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Antenna Calibrations Using Radio Sources, H. Hardebeck, 11/65 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - A Correcting Feed at 611 MHz for the AIO Reflector, G. Perona, 2/66 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - For the Design, Construction & Testing of a 611 MHz Linearly Polarized Line Feed, T. Gold, NSF Proposal, 11/67-4/68 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Geometric Calibration of Arecibo 1000-ft Reflector, W. Philipson, 6/68 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - James Condon, 1968-72
      - "Cosine Squared" Point Feeds for the Arecibo Reflector - Numerical Results, J. Condon, 2/68 (Box 45, Folder 35)
      - Theory of Point Fed Spherical Reflectors, J. Condon, 6/69 (Box 45, Folder 36)
      - Observational Tests of the 430 MHz Line Feeds, Condon & Abreu, 10/72 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - Allan Love, 1963-1979
      - Theoretical & Experimental Investigation Leading to Design & Construction of a Broadband Line Source Illuminator, 6/63 (Box 45, Folder 38)
      - A Circularly Polarized TM11 Mode Launcher for the Arecibo Line Source Feed, 7-12-66 (Box 45, Folder 39)
      - Arecibo Scale Model Line Feed Design, Interim Technical Report, 3-15-67 (Box 45, Folder 40)
      - Experimental Line Feed Development Program, 5-10-67 (Box 45, Folder 41)
      - Scale Model Development of a Feed for the Arecibo Spherical Reflector at 611 MHz, Final Report, 2-24-69 (Box 45, Folder 42)
      - Arecibo 430 MHz Feed Development Study,First Quarterly Engineering Report, Jan 1970 (Box 45, Folder 43)
      - Arecibo 430 MHz Feed Development Study, Final Engineering Report, April 1971 (Box 45, Folder 44)
      - Advanced Feed Techniques for the Arecibo Spherical Reflector, Allan Love, 3-18-77 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Progress Reports: Study of Advanced Feed Development Techniques for the Arecibo Spherical Reflector, 12/77-12/78 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Advanced Feed Techniques for the Arecibo Spherical Reflector, Allan Love, Rockwell Int'l, May 1979 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Gregorian Feed Concepts for the Arecibo Telescope, F.D. Drake, Nov 1980 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - 430 MHz Transmitter Modulator Upgrade Design, G.E. Tallmadge, 7/81 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Sebastian von Hoerner
      - Correspondence, Gregorian Feed concept, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Arecibo Three Mirror Systems, III: Revised Force Estimates for Selected Systems, May 1983 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Gregorian Feed Scientific Justification Survey, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Per-Simon Kildal, 1986-94
      - Study of Element Patterns & Excitations of the Line Feeds of the Spherical Reflector Antenna in Arecibo, Per-Simon Kildal, IEEE, 2/86 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Areciibo-Antenna Upgrading (NAIC), Project Memo, May 1986 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Studies of dual-reflector feed for the Arecibo Observatory Radio Telescope - Final Report,1/89 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Novel ray techniques to synthesize and analyze multi-reflector antennas including edge diffracton losses, 6/89 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Diffraction analysis of a proposed dual-reflector feed for the spherical reflector antenna of the Arecibo Observatory, Sep-Oct 1989 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Improved Element Pattern for the Line Feeds of the Spherical Reflector Antenna in Arecibo, 12/89 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Laws of geometrical optics mapping in multi-reflector antennas with application to elliptical apertures, 12/89 (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - Asymptotic Transition Region Theory for Edge Diffraction Part I: Tracing Transition Regions via Reflectors; Asymptotic Transition Region Theory for Edge Diffraction Part II, Calculation of Diffraction Losses in Multireflector Antennas; Diffraction Analysis of Line Feeds for Spherical Reflector, 9/90 (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - Synthesis of Multi-Reflector Antennas by Kinematic & Dynamic Ray Tracing; Analysis of Numerically Specified Multi-Reflector Antennas by Kinematic & Dynamic Ray Tracing, 10/90 (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - Development of a Dual-Reflector Feed for the Arecibo Radio Telescope: An Overview; IEEE Antennas & Propagation, Oct 1991 (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - Studies of tolerances, point feeding and cluster feeding of the Gregorian dual-reflector feed for the Arecibo radio telescope, 4/92 (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - The Arecibo Upgrading: Electrical Design and Expected Performance of the Dual-Reflector Feed System, Proc. IEEE, May 1994 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Evolution of Receivers & Feed Systems, George Peter, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Phil Perillat- 430 linefeeds 7-18-99 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Arecibo HF Antenna Feed System Additional Electrical Feasibility Issues, J. Breakall & M. Jacobs, Sept 2000 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - CSIRO, 2002-2003
      - A 7-Element L-Band Multibeam Feed for the Arecibo Radio Telescope, 12-19-02 (Box 46, Folder 24)
      - Tests on an Element of the Mutlibeam Feed for the Arecibo Radio Telescope, 1-28-03 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Merle LaLonde, 1966-74
      - A High-Performance Line Source Feed for the AIO Spherical Reflector, CRSR 329, 2/69 (Box 46, Folder 26)
      - Lab Notes: 327 MHz feed, 430 H.P. feed, 1966-74 (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - Lab Notes: 2380 D.P. feed, 1667 D.P. feed, 1975-76 (Box 46, Folder 28)
      - Three Highly Efficient Line Feeds for the Arecibo Spherical Reflector Telescope, CRSR 385, 196? (Box 46, Folder 29)
      - Aberration-Correcting Line Feeds, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 30)
      - The Design of Linear Polarized Slotted Waveguide Feeds for Spherical Reflectors, 4/77 (Box 46, Folder 31)
      - Lab Notes: 3000 MHz test feed, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 32)
      - LaLonde Obituary 1977 (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - Eddie Castro
      - Lab Notes: Line Feeds, Book 1 (Castro), 10/75-3/77 (Box 46, Folder 34)
      - Lab Notes: Line Feeds, Book 2 (Castro), 7/75- (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - NAIC Lab Files
    - Feed Test Selection Data, mid to late 1970s (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - TS3 data, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - TS4 data, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Misc. GBT, 1989-90 (Box 46, Folder 39)
    - Technical memos-Jon Hagen, 1989-91 (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Technical memos-Jose Maldonado, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 41)
    - Technical memos-Paul Stetson, 1990-91 (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - Technical memos-Mike Davis, 1990-92 (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - Lynn Baker notes & viewgraphs, upgrade meetings, 1990s (Box 46, Folder 44)
    - Upgrade & Ground Screen misc., 1990s (Box 46, Folder 45)
    - C-Band 6-8 GHz receiver, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - 6-8 GHz Thermal Transition, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - 430 MHz 1/2 wave, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Rx shutter, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - L-Band horn, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - C-Band drawings 3.9 to 5.8 GHz, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - C-Band taper & adaptor, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - C-Band 4-6 GHz, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - C-Band horn drawing, Rev. 1, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - S-Band "D" mounts, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - 430 horn mounts; 430 waveguide flanges, etc., 1995 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Collector, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - S-Band septum polarizer, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - S-Band receive horn, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - 327 Dewar, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - S-Band transmitter horn, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Half height turnstile, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - L-Band, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - 430 Dewar, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Hair pin, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Target, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - ALFA mount, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Torque meter, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - He Filter, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Chassis frames cabinets etc. rotary floor shields, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Receiver systems, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Sheave, 1998-00 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Tertiary sub-reflector assemblies, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Cable carriage, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Encoder, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Monoplexer, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Mini Dewar #1, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Rectangular Mini Dewar #2, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - Teflon disc anchors, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - HF Transmission Lines, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Gregorian Dewar 16K Mounting Brackets, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - Pin & conductor assembly, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - ALFA RFI Aperture Shield, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 38)
    - ALFA System Mount, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 39)
    - Rotary floor encoder, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 40)
    - Test dewar (Arecibo), 1993 (Box 47, Folder 41)
    - Rotary coupler & drawings- S-Band, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 42)
    - Eq Disposal, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 43)
    - X-Band horn 8-10 GHz, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    - Finline OMT, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 45)
    - Azimuth encoder housing, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 46)
    - Distomats, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 47)
    - 35/50 OHM Branchline 430, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 48)
    - Steel for rails, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 49)
    - Tertiary, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 50)
    - Leaf spring, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 51)
    - S-Band transmitter horn shutter, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 52)
    - 8-10 GHz drawings, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 53)
    - Scalar Horn L-Band 1.0-1.8 GHz, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 54)
    - S-Band shutter design, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 55)
    - Lynn Baker Files
      - Advanced Feeds Study, First Interim Report,L. Baker, 2/81 (Box 47, Folder 56)
      - Ground Screen Ray Tracing Analysis, L. Baker, 8/84 (Box 47, Folder 57)
      - Reflector Shapes Versus Aperture Shapes, L. Baker, 2/85 (Box 47, Folder 58)
      - Analysis of Survey Data Taken in June 1999, L. Baker (Box 47, Folder 59)
      - Survey related drawings (no dates) (Box 47, Folder 60)
      - Primary survey memos, 1983-84 (Box 47, Folder 61)
      - Survey theory & derivations (Box 47, Folder 62)
      - Primary measure with cart, 3/98 (Box 47, Folder 63)
      - Sokkia calibrations, 1/99 (Box 47, Folder 64)
      - Azimuth ring gear survey, 2/00 (Box 47, Folder 65)
      - Rail shape data, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 66)
      - Old platform & dome calibrations, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 67)
      - Gregorian jacking, 10/98 (Box 47, Folder 68)
      - Films of secondary (Box 47, Folder 69)
      - A&W/Vellozzi memos & notes, 1994, 2001-03 (Box 47, Folder 70)
      - A&W condition report & related, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 71)
      - Cable sag measure & analysis, platform weight, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 72)
      - Gregorian dome weight, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 73)
      - Lucius Pitkin - antenna support wheel, 8/06 (Box 47, Folder 74)
      - MERLAB - elevation wheel & track life, 5/07 (Box 47, Folder 75)
      - Tiger Team, general, admin & minutes, 2006-07 (Box 47, Folder 76)
      - Misc. Drawings (1 of 2) (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Misc. Drawings (2 of 2) (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Maple Ave Lab Establishment, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Secondary adjustment initial installation, 5/96 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Secondary panel install, 5/96 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Panel fab. Data notes & misc., 1/95 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Panel gap data, secondary, 9/95 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Tertiary panels, 5/96 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Optics alignment, 11/95-2/96 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Tertiary Vertex plate/ranor, 12/95 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Vertex plate, measurer analysis, 5/96 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Dome/secondary interference, 11/93 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Exit pupil, 7/94 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Subreflector panels, 1990s (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Panel verification, Kildal, 4/95 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Zenith angle coverage, 11/93 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Secondary deflection study, 4/93 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - Tertiary frame, field assembly, 3/95 (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Old tertiary frame stuff, 4/95-6/95 (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Tertiary space frame, Lynn Baker concept, 2/95 (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - Secondary panels (RSI), 8/94 (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - Tertiary panel adjust on rim road, 9/96 (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - Tertiary panel layout, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 23)
      - Tertiary align archives, 11/96 (Box 48, Folder 24)
      - Tertiary space frame and mounting, 2/96 (Box 48, Folder 25)
      - Misc. tech notes, upgrade, 1989-95 (Box 48, Folder 26)
      - Tertiary position system & theory, 1/96 (Box 48, Folder 27)
      - Tertiary motion algorithm, 4/96 (Box 48, Folder 28)
      - Tertiary actuators, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 29)
      - Tertiary skirt, 7/03 (Box 48, Folder 30)
      - Tertiary drive info, 11/01 (Box 48, Folder 31)
      - Old tertiary adjustment table, 10/04 (Box 48, Folder 32)
      - Tertiary survey notes, 10/04 (Box 48, Folder 33)
      - Videogrammetry of secondary, 11/03 (Box 48, Folder 34)
      - Secondary survey plots & analysis, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 35)
      - Misc. Secondary notes, 2003-04 (Box 48, Folder 36)
      - Secondary: missed targets, code targets, tasks, 2/04 (Box 48, Folder 37)
      - Previous survey results, 2002, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 38)
      - Old, obs., wrong, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 39)
      - AO9 survey, 8/01 (Box 48, Folder 40)
      - Dome position data from AO9, 4/00 (Box 48, Folder 41)
      - AO9 survey scale factor, 3/01 (Box 48, Folder 42)
      - Location of AO9, 7/97 (Box 48, Folder 43)
      - Platform align miscellaneous, 2/02 (Box 48, Folder 44)
      - Survey modeling, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 45)
      - Pupil target mounts, 8/01 (Box 48, Folder 46)
      - AO9 target analysis optical center of cubes, 10/01 (Box 48, Folder 47)
      - Distomat data, platform tilt, 9/97 (Box 48, Folder 48)
      - Tilt sensors & misc., 1992 (Box 48, Folder 49)
      - Feed tower deflection, 3/96 (Box 48, Folder 50)
      - Old survey logs, 10/97-11/97 (Box 48, Folder 51)
      - Elevation rail shim (archives), 7/97 (Box 48, Folder 52)
      - Sounding data, 11/97 (Box 48, Folder 53)
      - Phil Perillat data & notes, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 54)
    - FEEDS, 1968-1985
      - 1415 Dual polarization feed, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - 1220 Flat feed, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - 1320 feed, flat 16 deg, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - 1360 dual polarizatin feed (no date) (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - 1415 feed, guys mount, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - 834 40 ft feed, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - 834 feed, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - 932 MHz 15 deg flat feed, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - 1020 MHz flat feed, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - 1020 MHz feed, 23 deg - 40 ft flat, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - 1120 MHz flat feed, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - 611 MHz feed, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Autonetics 611 feed, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - 760 MHz feed, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - 327 Mc tests, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - 318 feed, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - 510 MHz feed, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Feed mounting info (to Carrriage House), 1977 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Feed theory misc., 1977 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - 460 MHz Feed test, 1977 or 1978 (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - 470 MHz Feed, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - Auto focus mount, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Fairing tool, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 23)
      - Phase data all feeds, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 24)
      - 3 GHz mixers, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 25)
      - Dual frequency parabolic feed 8.31 & 1.20 GHz, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 26)
      - Test section data - Ed Castro, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 27)
      - 4830 feed support, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 28)
      - 4.91 GHz line feed, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 29)
      - Waveguide flanges, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 30)
      - Feed displacement frequency shift, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 31)
      - 2695 feed patterns & measurements, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 32)
      - 3000 MHz feed, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 33)
      - 4830 Feed #1 Empirical Design, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 34)
      - 2270.4 feed, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 35)
      - 2380 flat feed, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 36)
      - 2480 feed 15 deg flat (not built), 1977 (Box 49, Folder 37)
      - 2600 feed 15 ft, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 38)
      - 2380 dual polarization feed, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 39)
      - 1667 MHz line feed flat, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - 1773 MHz 15 deg flat feed, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - New 2380 feed, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - 1415 turnstile junction, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - 1420 feed flat, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - 1667 dual polarization line feed, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Main reflector scalloping (no date) (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Waveguide equalizer, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - 40' line feeds (no date) (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - 50 MHz feed, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Feed Notes (no dates) (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Line Feed Notes (1985 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - 1120 Feed design, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - 2380 feed test, AIO, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Alpha measure, late 1970s (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - β-α TS plots, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Dipole loaded test section, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Test section design & data, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - TS-A FF data plots, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - TS-B FF data & plots, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - TS-C FF data & plots, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - 1969 Univ. of Sydney Proposal to NASA for Studies of the Ionosphere (Box 50, Folder 22)
      - Arecibo Message of November 1974 (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - Viking Landing 1975 (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - Past Arecibo Brochures & other public outreach materials (Box 50, Folder 25)
      - Scale drawing of Arecibo vs. Washington Monument, Green Bank Telescope, Eiffel Tower (Box 50, Folder 26)
      - 1997 Arecibo Gregorian Inauguration (Box 50, Folder 27)
      - IEEE Milestone Dedication, 11/3/01 (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - Univ. of Puerto Rico Collaborations, 1997, 1999, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 29)
      - 40th Anniversary, 11/1/03 (Box 50, Folder 30)